A Finding Aid to the Evangeline J. Montgomery Papers, 1928-2018, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Unidentified Audiovisual Material, circa 1990s; Series 9; Archival Resource Key; 1 Folder
  - Unidentified Audiovisual Material, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key; 2 Videocassettes (VHS); 1 Sound cassettes (microcassette); 1 Sound cassette (Box 25, Folder 21)